Guide to the Stanford University Website Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Schools, 2010-2011; Series 2
  - Medicine, 2010-2011
    - Institute for Immunity Transplantation and Infection, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 6, iti201110; 13 megabyte(s) (181 files in 36 directories)
      - 2012 Aug 6, iti20120806; 24 megabyte(s) (119 files in 21 directories)
      - Immunology, 2012
        - 2012 Dec 5, immunol20121205; 68.6 megabyte(s) (235 files in 24 Folders)
    - Institute for Stem Cell Biology and Regenerative Medicine, 2011
      - 2011 Oct 10, stemcell201110; 85.7 megabyte(s) (279 files in 65 directories)
      - Center for Human Embryonic Stem Cell Research and Education, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 11, hesc201110; 5.38 megabyte(s) (151 files in 35 directories)
        - 2012 Nov 28, hesc20121128; 6.23 megabyte(s) (84 files in 17 directories)
    - Institutional Research and Academic Career Development Award, 2011
      - 2011 Oct 13, 0.98 megabyte(s) (89 files in 23 directories)
    - Integrative Medicine Interest Group, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 13, imig201110; 44 megabyte(s) (113 files in 27 directories)
      - 2012 Dec 4, imig20121204; 43.1 megabyte(s) (42 files in 7 directories)
    - Li Ka Shing Center for Learning and Knowledge, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 13, lksc201110; 3.86 megabyte(s) (161 files in 51 directories)
      - 2012 Dec 4, lksc20121204; (79 files in 19 directories)
    - Masters of Science in Medicine Degree Program
      - 2011 Oct 17, msm201110; 0.78 megabyte(s) (88 files in 35 directories)
    - Medical Education, Office of, 2011
    - Medical Scientist Training Program, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 18, mstp201110; 31.6 megabyte(s) (156 files in 45 directories)
      - 2012 Dec 5, mstp20121205; 1280 megabyte(s) (89 files in 14 directories)
    - Medicine, Department of, 2010-2012
      - 2010 Dec 14, 19 megabyte(s) (302 files in 32 directories)
      - 2011 Sep 14, 48.1 megabyte(s) (442 files in 80 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, medicine20120611; 43.8 megabyte(s) (416 files in 84 directories)
      - Blood and Marrow Transplantation Program, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 20, bmt201109; 57.7 megabyte(s) (176 files in 50 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 28, bmt20120628; 30.1 megabyte(s) (150 files in 50 directories)
      - Cardiovascular Medicine, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 20, cvmed201109; 42 megabyte(s) (349 files in 54 directories)
      - Center for Research in Disease Prevention, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Jul 20, prev201107; 10.5 megabyte(s) (193 files in 47 directories)
        - Health Promotion Research Center, 2011
          - 2011 Oct 3, hprc201110; 4.38 megabyte(s) (169 files in 30 directories)
        - 2012 Apr 20, prevention20120420; 9.86 megabyte(s) (165 files in 47 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 28, cvmedicine20120628; 43 megabyte(s) (337 files in 52 directories)
      - Digestive Disease Center, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 20, ddc201109; 3.32 megabyte(s) (109 files in 23 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 9, ddc20120628; 6.33 megabyte(s) (111 files in 23 directories)
      - Endocrinology, Gerontology and Metabolism, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 20, endoc201109; 1.36 megabyte(s) (113 files in 31 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 28, endocrinology20120628; 1.34 megabyte(s) (116 files in 31 directories)
      - Gastroenterology and Hepatology,Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 20, gastrohep201109; 5.62 megabyte(s) (115 files in 35 directories)
        - 2012 Jul 9, gastrohep20120628; 5.56 megabyte(s) (119 files in 35 directories)
      - General Medical Disciplines, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 20, gmd201109; 44.9 megabyte(s) (238 files in 39 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 28, gmd20120628; 11.8 megabyte(s) (215 files in 35 directories)
        - Clinical Excellence Research Center, 2011-2012
          - 2011 Oct 12, cerc201110; 6.14 megabyte(s) (125 files in 31 directories)
          - 2012 Nov 29, cerc20121129; 9.9 megabyte(s) (143 files in 23 directories)
        - Hospice and Pallative Medicine, 2011-2012
          - 2011 Sep 20, hospice201109; 12.2 megabyte(s) (137 files in 30 directories)
          - 2012 Jun 28, hospice20120628; 12.1 megabyte(s) (137 files in 34 directories)
        - Primary Care Associate Program, 2012
          - 2012 Aug 28, pcap20120828; 11.7 megabyte(s) (127 files in 14 directories)
      - Hematology, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 20, hema201109; 3.5 megabyte(s) (182 files in 38 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 28, hematology20120628; 3.08 megabyte(s) (169 files in 39 directories)
      - Immunology and Rheumatology, Division of, 2011
        - 2011 Sep 20, immu201109; 0.97 megabyte(s) (103 files in 29 directories)
        - C. Garrison Fathman Laboratory of Cellular and Molecular Immunology, 2012
          - 2012 Jul 26, fathman20120725; 276 megabyte(s) (74 files in 8 directories)
        - Robinson Lab, 2012
          - 2012 Sep 24, robinson20120924; 188 megabyte(s) (373 files in 59 directories)
      - Infectious Diseases and Geographic Medicine, 2011
        - Chronic Fatigue Initiative, 2011-2012
          - 2011 Oct 10, chronicfatigue201110; 4.04 megabyte(s) (144 files in 45 directories)
          - 2012 Sep 4, chronicfatigue20120904; 4.58 megabyte(s) (78 files in 25 directories)
      - Oncology, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 20, onco201109; 2.67 megabyte(s) (165 files in 41 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 29, oncology20120629; 2.53 megabyte(s) (167 files in 39 directories)
      - Pulmonary and Critical Care Medicine, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Sep 20, pulmo201109; 776 megabyte(s) (146 files in 56 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 29, pulmonary20120629; 678 megabyte(s) (302 files in 103 directories)
      - Resource Guide, 2012
        - 2012 Dec 11, domrg20121211; 28.9 megabyte(s) (205 files in 37 directories)
      - Utz Lab, 2012
        - 2012 Nov 9, utz20121109; 141 megabyte(s) (210 files in 19 directories)
    - Microbiology and Immunology, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, microim201109; 1.45 megabyte(s) (97 files in 23 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, microimmuno20120611; 1.34 megabyte(s) (102 files in 23 directories)
    - Molecular and Cellular Physiology, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, mcp201109; 11.7 megabyte(s) (155 files in 34 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, mcp20120611; 11 megabyte(s) (159 files in 34 directories)
      - Nelson Lab, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 31, nelson20120731; 593 megabyte(s) (377 files in 33 directories)
    - Molecular Imaging Program at Stanford, 2012
      - 2012 Dec 10, mips20121210; 1833 megabyte(s) (2372 files in 417 directories)
    - Multidisciplinary Cutaneous Lymphoma Group, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 14, cutaneous201110; 126 megabyte(s) (124 files in 29 directories)
      - 2012 Dec 5, cutaneous20121205; 58.1 megabyte(s) (59 files in 11 directories)
    - Multidisciplinary Program in Immunology, 2011
      - 2011 Oct 14, immunology201110; 106 megabyte(s) (322 files in 41 directories)
    - Network for Translational Research in Optical Imaging, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 14, ntroi201110; 26.5 megabyte(s) (123 files in 24 directories)
      - 2012 Dec 5, ntroi20121205; 26 megabyte(s) (57 files in 6 directories)
    - Neurology and Neurological Sciences, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2012 Jul 9, neurology20120709; 40.2 megabyte(s) (411 files in 69 directories)
      - Huguenard Lab, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 26, huguenard20120726; 9.13 megabyte(s) (93 files in 13 directories)
      - Stroke Center, 2011-2013
        - 2011 Aug 31, stroke201108; 47.8 megabyte(s)
        - 2012 May 23, strokecenter20120523; 54.8 megabyte(s) (228 files in 49 directories)
        - 2013 May 8, strokecenter20130508; 101 megabyte(s) (143 files in 11 directories)
      - Steinman Lab, 2012
        - 2012 Oct 30, steinman20121030; 2.2 megabyte(s) (63 files in 3 directories)
      - Wyss-Coray Lab, 2012
        - 2012 Nov 9, twclab20121109; 15.8 megabyte(s) (123 files in 45 directories)
    - Neurobiology, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, neurob201109; 0.71 megabyte(s) (85 files in 20 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, neurobiology20120611; 0.76 megabyte(s) (90 files in 20 directories)
      - Jennifer Raymond Lab, 2012
        - 2012 Sep 24, raymond20120924; 70.1 megabyte(s) (61 files in 8 directories)
    - Neuroscience in Women's Health, Center for, 2011-2013
      - 2011 Aug 12, cnwh201108; 1.92 megabyte(s) (94 files in 28 directories)
      - 2012 May 21, womensneuro20120521; 1.96 megabyte(s) (99 files in 28 directories)
      - 2013 May 6, womensneuroscience20130506; 1.37 megabyte(s) (25 files in 10 directories)
    - Neurosurgery, Department of, 2012
      - 2012 Jul 9, neurosurgery20120709; 137 megabyte(s) (483 files in 46 directories)
    - Nolan Lab, 2012
      - 2012 Jul 31, nolan20120731; 10.2 megabyte(s) (382 files in 46 directories)
    - Obstetrics and Gynecology, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, obgyn201109; 4.42 megabyte(s) (171 files in 42 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, obgyn20120611; 4.22 megabyte(s) (163 files in 42 directories)
    - Opthamology, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, opthal201109; 7.74 megabyte(s) (197 files in 30 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, opthamology20120611; 5.84 megabyte(s) (188 files in 29 directories)
    - Orthopedic Surgery, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, ortho201109; 35.3 megabyte(s) (456 files in 51 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, 28.4 megabyte(s) (436 files in 52 directories)
      - Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2012
        - 2012 Dec 11, pmr20121211; 4.47 megabyte(s) (67 files in 8 directories)
    - Otolaryngology, Department of, 2012
      - Initiative to Cure Hearing Loss, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 25, hearing20120725; 12.6 megabyte(s) (178 files in 131 directories)
    - Pathology, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, path201109; 12.6 megabyte(s) (156 files in 34 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, pathology20120611; 14 megabyte(s) (156 files in 34 directories)
      - Autopsy Pathology, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, autopsy201110; 4.53 megabyte(s) (86 files in 21 directories)
        - 2012 Jul 2, autopsy20120702; 4.57 megabyte(s) (91 files in 21 directories)
      - Clinical Biochemical Genetics Laboratory, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, biochemgen201110; 1.62 megabyte(s) (102 files in 22 directories)
        - 2012 Jul 5, biochemgen20120705; 1.66 megabyte(s) (107 files in 22 directories)
      - Clinical Chemistry and Immunology Service, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, ccis201110; 186 megabyte(s) (275 files in 34 directories)
        - 2012 Jul 7, clinicalchem20120705; 2.59 megabyte(s) (99 files in 21 directories)
      - Clinical Microbiology, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, clinmicro201110; 3.45 megabyte(s) (96 files in 21 directories)
        - 2012 Jul 5, clinicalmicro20120705; 1.2 megabyte(s) (102 files in 21 directories)
      - Clinical Virology Laboratory, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, clinviro201110; 1.16 megabyte(s) (93 files in 22 directories)
        - 2012 Jul 5, clinicalviro20120705; 1.2 megabyte(s) (98 files in 22 directories)
      - Cytogenetics Laboratory, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, cytogen201110; 0.68 megabyte(s) (88 files in 21 directories)
        - 2012 Jul 5, cytogenetics20120705; 0.72 megabyte(s) (93 files in 21 directories)
      - Cytopathology Service, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, cytopath201110; 1.65 megabyte(s) (91 files in 22 directories)
        - 2012 Jul 5, cytopathology20120705; 1.68 megabyte(s) (96 files in 22 directories)
      - Dermatopathology Service, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, dermato201110; 6.43 megabyte(s) (101 files in 23 directories)
        - 2012 Jul 5, dermatopathology20120705; 6.97 megabyte(s) (108 files in 23 directories)
      - Hematopathology Laboratory, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, hemato201110; 1.14 megabyte(s) (94 files in 21 directories)
        - 2012 Jul 5, hematopathology20120705; 1.18 megabyte(s) (99 files in 21 directories)
      - Immunodiagnosis Service, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, immunodiag201110; 0.79 megabyte(s) (87 files in 21 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, immunodiagnosis20120801; 0.31 megabyte(s) (23 files in 5 directories)
      - Molecular Genetic Pathology Service, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, molgen201110; 2.58 megabyte(s) (91 files in 21 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, moleculargenetics20120801; 2.12 megabyte(s) (27 files in 5 directories)
      - Neuropathology Service, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, neuropath201110; 0.83 megabyte(s) (90 files in 22 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, neuropathology20120801; 0.37 megabyte(s) (924 files in 6 directories)
      - Renal Pathology Consultation Service, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, renalpath201110; 0.67 megabyte(s) (84 files in 21 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, renalpathology20120801; 0.21 megabyte(s) (20 files in 5 directories)
      - Surgical Pathology Diagnostic Services, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, surgpath201110; 1.15 megabyte(s) (85 files in 21 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, surgicalpathology20120801; 0.94 megabyte(s) (24 files in 5 directories)
      - Transfusion Service, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, transfus201110; 1.11 megabyte(s) (99 files in 22 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 6, transfusionmedicine20120801; 0.65 megabyte(s) (35 files in 6 directories)
    - Patient Education, 2011-2013
      - 2011 Aug 15, pated201108; 21.2 megabyte(s) (329 files in 36 directories)
      - 2012 May 21, patiented20120521; 19.2 megabyte(s) (326 files in 38 directories)
      - 2013 May 6, patiented20130506; 20.1 megabyte(s) (249 files in 20 directories)
    - Pediatric Advocacy Program, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 18, pedsadvocacy201110; 69.4 megabyte(s) (270 files in 58 directories)
      - 2012 Dec 5, pedsadvocacy20121205; 52 megabyte(s) (178 files in 41 directories)
    - Pediatric Bipolar Disorders Program, 2012
      - 2012 Dec 11, pediatricbipolar20121211; 24.4 megabyte(s) (59 files in 9 directories)
    - Pediatrics, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, pedi201109; 8.2 megabyte(s) (169 files in 42 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 11, pediatrics20120611; 3.66 megabyte(s) (161 files in 41 directories)
      - Adolescent Medicine, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, adolmed201110; 0.78 megabyte(s) (93 files in 27 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, adolescent20120801; 0.29 megabyte(s) (24 files in 10 directories)
      - Bass Center of Excellence in Pediatric Cancer and Blood Diseases, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, hemon201110; 1.68 megabyte(s) (118 files in 29 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, hemonstem20120801; 1.03 megabyte(s) (44 files in 11 directories)
      - Critical Care Medicine, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, pedcrit201110; 0.66 megabyte(s) (92 files in 25 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, pedcriticalcare20120801; 0.14 megabyte(s) (18 files in 8 directories)
      - General Pediatrics, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, genpeds201110; 4.48 megabyte(s) (141 files in 34 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, genpeds20120801; 3.91 megabyte(s) (64 files in 14 directories)
      - Immunology and Allergy, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, pedim201110; 1.76 megabyte(s) (93 files in 27 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, neonatology20120801; 1.28 megabyte(s) (25 files in 10 directories)
      - Kay Lab, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 30, kaylab20120730; 202 megabyte(s) (311 files in 18 directories)
      - Medical Genetics, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, medgen201110; 0.79 megabyte(s) (94 files in 27 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, medicalgenetics20120801; 0.39 megabyte(s) (26 files in 10 directories)
      - Neonatal and Developmental Medicine, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, neona201110; 34.7 megabyte(s) (264 files in 45 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, neonatology20120801; 20.7 megabyte(s) (189 files in 27 directories)
        - Mid-Coastal California Perinatal Outreach Program, 2011-2012
          - 2011 Oct 14, mccpop201110; 27.8 megabyte(s) (110 files in 28 directories)
          - 2012 Dec 4, mccpop20121204; 29.4 megabyte(s) (35 Files in 7 directories)
      - Neuro-Oncology Program, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, neuronc201110; 0.61 megabyte(s) (85 files in 24 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, neuronc20120801; 0.14 megabyte(s) (16 files in 7 folders)
      - Pediatric Cancer Biology Program, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, pedcan201110; 0.7 megabyte(s) (86 files in 25 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, pedcancerbio20120801; 0.22 megabyte(s) (17 files in 8 directories)
      - Pediatric Cardiology, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, pedcar201110; 1.54 megabyte(s) (113 files in 28 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, pedcard20120801; 0.99 megabyte(s) (45 files in 11 directories)
      - Pediatric Endocrinology and Diabetes, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, dped201110; 21.1 megabyte(s) (213 files in 54 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 6, dped20120801; 14.9 megabyte(s) (128 files in 39 directories)
      - Pediatric Hematology and Oncology, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, pedhem201110; 0.61 megabyte(s) (85 files in 24 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, pedhemeonc20120801; 0.1 megabyte(s) (16 files in 5 directories)
      - Pediatric Nephrology, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, pedneph201110; 69.4 megabyte(s) (175 files in 29 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, neuronc20120801; 65.4 megabyte(s) (96 files in 13 directories)
      - Pediatric Rheumatology Program, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 4, pedrh201110; 1.14 megabyte(s) (105 files in 28 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, pedrheumatology20120801; 0.69 megabyte(s) (37 files in 11 directories)
      - Pulmonary Medicine, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 3, pedpul201110; 0.98 megabyte(s) (89 files in 27 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 8, pedpulmonary20120801; 0.5 megabyte(s) (21 files in 10 directories)
      - Stem Cell Transplantation, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 4, sct201110; 0.64 megabyte(s) (96 files in 24 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, sct20120801; 0.16 megabyte(s) (17 files in 7 directories)
    - Proteomics Center, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 3, proteo201110; 15.6 megabyte(s) (319 files in 47 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 12, proteomics20121112; 5.91 megabyte(s) (192 files in 36 directories)
    - Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, psychia201109; 19.3 megabyte(s) (189 files in 40 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 6, psychiatry20120608; 57.3 megabyte(s) (257 files in 43 directories)
      - Adjunct Clinical Faculty Association, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 10, acfa201110; 0.79 megabyte(s) (82 files in 23 directories)
        - 2012 Nov 6, acf20121106; 0.64 megabyte(s) (20 files in 5 directories)
      - Center for Psychiatry and the Law, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 4, psychlaw201110; 0.92 megabyte(s) (97 files in 23 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 8, psychlaw20120801; 0.47 megabyte(s) (32 files in 7 directories)
      - Center on Stress and Health, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 4, stress201110; 10.6 megabyte(s) (209 files in 37 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, stresshealth20120801; 14 megabyte(s) (141 files in 22 directories)
      - Child and Adolescent Psychiatry and Child Development, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 4, childpsych201110; 39.5 megabyte(s) (122 files in 31 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, childpsychiatry20120801; 37.9 megabyte(s) (86 files in 20 directories)
      - Early Life Stress Research Program, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 18, elsrp201110; 74.3 megabyte(s) (87 files in 22 directories)
        - 2012 Dec 5, elsrp20121205; 1.5 megabyte(s) (47 files in 15 dirctories)
      - Eating Disorders Research Program, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 4, edres201110; 1.03 megabyte(s) (93 files in 21 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, edresearch20120801; 0.56 megabyte(s) (24 files in 5 directories)
      - Laboratory for the Study of Behavioral Medicine, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 4, bml201110; 22.9 megabyte(s) (108 files in 35 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, bml20120801; 22.4 megabyte(s) (42 files in 14 directories)
      - Obsessive-Compulsive Disorders Program, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 4, ocd201110; 0.99 megabyte(s) (96 files in 26 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, ocd20120801; 0.54 megabyte(s) (32 files in 10 directories)
      - Psychiatry and Law, 2012
        - 2012 Dec 11, forensicpsychology20121211; 18.3 megabyte(s) (31 files in 7 directories)
      - Stanford/VA Alzheimer's Research Center, 2011-2013
        - 2011 Jul 1, svalz201107; 105 megabyte(s) (166 files in 23 directories)
        - 2012 Apr 13, svalz20120413; 105 megabyte(s) (169 files in 23 directories)
        - 2013 Apr 8, svalz20130408; 75.4 megabyte(s) (83 files in 5 directories)
    - Radiological Sciences Laboratory, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Aug 5-7, rsl201108; 976 megabyte(s) (1989 files in 216 directories)
      - 2012 May 8, rsl20120508; 1136.6 megabyte(s) (1,954 Files, 206 Folders)
    - Radiation Oncology, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, radonc201109; 3.79 megabyte(s) (139 files in 132 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 8, radonc20120608; 3.32 megabyte(s) (141 files in 33 directories)
    - Radiology, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, radio201109; 165 megabyte(s) (2016 files in 132 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 7, radiology20120607; 1290.24 megabyte(s) (2671 files in 206 directories)
      - 3D and Quantitative Imaging, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 4, 3drad201110; 46.2 megabyte(s) (183 files in 30 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, 3drad20120801; 44.4 megabyte(s) (107 files in 14 directories)
      - Nuclear Medicine Clinic, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 4, nuclear201110; 10.9 megabyte(s) (254 files in 48 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, nuclearmedicine20120801; 19.9 megabyte(s) (195 files in 32 directories)
      - Pediatric Radiology, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 5, pedrad201110; 3.42 megabyte(s) (100 files in 26 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 1, pedrad20120801; 2.96 megabyte(s) (32 files in 10 directories)
    - Robert A. Chase Hand and Upper Limb Center, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 6, handsur201110; 1.65 megabyte(s) (97 files in 26 directories)
      - 2012 Aug 6, handsurgery20120806; 1.16 (29 files in 10 directories)
    - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation Physician Faculty Scholars Program, 2012
      - 2012 Sep 24, rwjfpfs20120924; 18.7 megabyte(s) (550 files in 52 directories)
    - Society of Physician Scholars, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 17, ssps201110; 52.6 megabyte(s) (225 files in 45 directories)
      - 2012 Dec 5, ssps20121205; 22.9 megabyte(s)
    - SPARK, 2012
      - 2012 Dec 11, sparkmed20121211; 2.13 megabyte(s) (52 files in 18 directories)
    - Spectrum Child Health, 2011
      - 2011 Oct 4, spectch201110; 4.48 megabyte(s) (128 files in 40 directories)
    - Spinal Muscular Atrophy Clinical Trials, 2011
      - 2011 Oct 3, sma201110; 3.32 megabyte(s) (100 files in 22 directories)
    - Stanford Center for Geonomics and Personalized Medicine, 2012
      - 2012 Dec 11, scpgm20121211; 12.5 megabyte(s) (122 files in 6 directories)
    - Stanford Institute for Neuro-Innovation and Translational Neuroscience, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 10, neuroscience201110; 40.6 megabyte(s) (282 files in 58 directories)
      - 2012 Sep 4, neuroscience20120904; 39.5 megabyte(s) (201 files in 35 directories)
    - Stanford-LPCH Vaccine Program, 2012
      - 2012 Nov 9, vaccines20121109; 2.68 megabyte(s) (76 files in 4 directories)
    - Stem Cell Biology and Regenerative Medicine Ph.D. Program, 2012
      - 2012 Dec 11, stemcellphd20121211; 4.04 megabyte(s) (95 files in 24 directories)
    - Structural Biology, 2012
      - 2012 Jul 9, structuralbio20120709; 3.02 megabyte(s) (139 files in 31 directories)
    - Surgery, Department of, 2011-2012